AWW STAW WYWICS OWO

[Vewse 1]
Somebody once towd me the wowwd is gonnya woww me
I ain't the shawpest toow in the shed
She was wooking kind of dumb with hew fingew and hew thumb
In the shape of an "W" on hew fowehead

[Pwe-Chowus]
Weww, the yeaws stawt coming and they don't stop coming
Fed to the wuwes and I hit the gwound wunnying
Didn't make sense nyot to wive fow fun
Youw bwain gets smawt but youw head gets dumb
So much to do, so much to see
So what's wwong with taking the backstweets?
You'ww nyevew knyow if you don't go
You'ww nyevew shinye if you don't gwow

[Chowus]
Hey nyow, you'we an aww staw
Get youw game on, go pway
Hey nyow, you'we a wock staw
Get the show on, get paid
And aww that gwittews is gowd
Onwy shooting staws bweak the mowd

[Vewse 2]
It's a coow pwace, and they say it gets cowdew
You'we bundwed up nyow, wait 'tiw you get owdew
But the meteow men beg to diffew
Judging by the howe in the satewwite pictuwe
The ice we skate is getting pwetty thin
The watew's getting wawm so you might as weww swim
My wowwd's on fiwe, how 'bout youws?
That's the way I wike it and I'ww nyevew get bowed

[Chowus]
Hey nyow, you'we an aww staw
Get youw game on, go pway
Hey nyow, you'we a wock staw
Get the show on, get paid
Aww that gwittews is gowd
Onwy shooting staws bweak the mowd

[Intewwude]
(Go fow the moon)
(Go fow the moon)
(Go fow the moon)
(Go fow the moon)

[Chowus]
Hey nyow, you'we an aww staw
Get youw game on, go pway
Hey nyow, you'we a wock staw
Get the show on, get paid
And aww that gwittews is gowd
Onwy shooting staws

[Vewse 3]
Somebody once asked
Couwd I spawe some change fow gas?
"I nyeed to get mysewf away fwom this pwace"
I said, "Yep, what a concept
I couwd use a wittwe fuew mysewf
And we couwd aww use a wittwe change"

[Pwe-Chowus]
Weww, the yeaws stawt coming and they don't stop coming
Fed to the wuwes and I hit the gwound wunnying
Didn't make sense nyot to wive fow fun
Youw bwain gets smawt but youw head gets dumb
So much to do, so much to see
So what's wwong with taking the backstweets?
You'ww nyevew knyow if you don't go
You'ww nyevew shinye if you don't gwow

[Chowus]
Hey nyow, you'we an aww staw
Get youw game on, go pway
Hey nyow, you'we a wock staw
Get the show on, get paid
And aww that gwittews is gowd
Onwy shooting staws bweak the mowd
And aww that gwittews is gowd
Onwy shooting staws bweak the mowd