FLEA MARKET MONTGOMERY LYRICS

Living rooms, bedrooms, dinettes, oh yeah
You can find 'em at the market
We talkin' 'bout Flea Market Montgomery
It's just like it's just like a mini mall
Oh yeah
Come shop with us, I said Flea Market Montgomery
It's just like, it's just like a mini mall
Hey hey, you heard me, come shop
Living rooms, bedrooms, dinettes we've got it
You need it you'll find it
It's just like, it's just like a mini mall
Hey hey, you heard me, come shop
I said, Flea Market Montgomery
It's just like, it's just like a mini mall
Hey hey!
Living rooms, bedrooms, dinettes, oh yeah
You can find 'em at the market
We talkin' 'bout Flea Market Montgomery
It's just like, it's just like a mini mall
Hey hey, don't stop, let's make it a dance
Come on now, to the left (to the left)
To the right (to the right)
Let's do this dance, hey, to the left (to the left)
To the right (to the right)
Let's make this a dance
Flea Market Montgomery
It gets you a-jumpin'
It's just like, it's just like a mini mall
Check it out now everybody
Like this, now, hey hey
Flea Market Montgomery
It's just like, it's just like a mini mall
Don't stop, let's dance
Flea Market Montgomery
It's just like it's just like a mini mall
(Let's break it on down now. Oh yeah, I know
You're gonna like this, come on now!)
It's just like (You know what I'm saying.)
It's just like (You know what I mean!)
It's just like (You know it, so why don't you
Just come on and see it.)
It's just like, it's just like a mini mall
(Ah yeah, you've seen it. It's just like, it's
Just like a mini mall. Ah yeah, you like this
Come on now, Flea Market.)